[A fire three years ago]
[took everything from me.]
[My husband,]
[my child,]
[Xiaoyu,]
[and the innocent, happy version of me.]
[They all died in that explosion.]
[Consumed by hatred,]
[I changed my appearance.]
[I was certain that Lin Jiming, the heir to the Lin Group,]
[was the real culprit behind it all.]
[I approached him]
[to reveal the truth]
[and make him pay.]
[I warned myself not to fall for him.]
[But his sincerity,]
[tenderness,]
[innocence,]
[and subtle favor]
[still messed with my heart.]
[Until the car accident,]
[the moment he risked his life to save mine,]
[I was completely torn.]
[He was my sworn enemy,]
[but also the one who stole my heart.]
[I finally realized]
[that the hardest battle to overcome]
[was never about revenge,]
[but]
[him.]
Mr. Lin,
this way.
He's here.
Here's the schedule for tonight's banquet.
This is the dance I learned just for you.
Lin Jiming,
watch carefully.
What's the biggest fear in a first impression?
It's mediocrity.
The key is to show your sexual tension
and uniqueness.
Only by standing out
can you become the target of attention.
Do you remember what the S in S club means?
Sexy.
Social.
Secret.
Eyes should be soft.
Posture should be firm.
Smile is a weapon.
Not an expression.
Not hold.
But pick.
Don't spill the wine.
Don't hide your smile.
Grace is not an act,
but a calculation.
Dancing is an excuse.
Touching is the purpose.
You have to make him feel
that you are guiding him,
not
he is controlling you.
Breathe lightly.
Use your eyes.
You are not dancing,
you are casting a net.
Others think you are the protagonist,
but they don't know
you are the real director.
Next,
it's your turn.
Mr. Wen is here.
Mr. Wen.
Nice to meet you, Mr. Wen.
Thank you all
for attending our Lin Group's charity gala.
I'd like to take this opportunity
to announce two things.
First,
I will gradually hand over the Lin Group
to my son,
Lin Jiming.
Secondly,
I'd like to introduce
Liu Yaruo,
the sister of our executive director,
Liu Yaping.
She and Jiming
will soon get engaged.
On the day
they get married,
Jiming will take full control
of the Lin Group.
Tian,
you look gorgeous today.
Many bosses asked me who you are.
Let's go.
Ms. Wei said
we should greet Mr. Zhang and Mr. Wang.
Okay.
Alright,
don't be so stiff.
If you want to see him,
just go ahead.
Alright.
Miss Liu
Jiming
What are you thinking about?
Nothing.
Actually, I didn't expect
Auntie Wen would suddenly
announce us in public.
I didn't agree.
Look at Yaru and Jiming.
What a perfect match.
Yaping
From now on,
we are family.
Thank you, Mr. Wen,
for the opportunities you gave me.
I wish our Lin Group
can be listed as soon as possible.
Yaping
will always be your soldier.
Good.
Thank you.
Was it because I didn't discuss it with you in advance
that you're upset?
Did you discuss with me
about me being your girlfriend?
You...
Pretty,
don't rush to leave.
You've got the moves,
now let's drink up!
Come on.
Have another drink with me.
Mr. Wang,
please behave yourself.
Let go.
Don't act all high and mighty.
You dancers are all the same.
Who's that?
Lin...
Mr. Lin.
Get lost.
Mr. Lin,
what do you mean?
I don't want to repeat myself.
Fine.
I'll leave.
You look tired.
Alcohol can ease sorrow,
but it can also cause trouble.
You'd better drink less.
The dance you just performed
was really good.
Don't put on airs.
Dancers like you
are all...
Who's there?
Alcohol can drown sorrows,
but it can also lead to trouble.
Better to drink less.
Thank you for your hard work today.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Bait is set,
waiting for you to take the hook.
Your idea was brilliant.
Two women dancing
is indeed more dynamic
and more enchanting.
I heard
the entire audience was in awe.
It's all thanks to your excellent coaching.
Well,
didn't you used to
refuse to attend these events?
Didn't you say
high-end events are our hunting grounds?
I'm not ready yet,
how dare I go into battle?
You sure know how to talk.
By the way,
Wei,
do you have a membership to the Beagle Club?
What?
You want to go there?
I heard
that club is really good,
so
I want to check it out.
Alright,
use my membership.
Isn't it boring
to play alone?
It's you.
What are you doing here?
Maybe
I'm here to meet you.
In that case,
let's have a game.
Okay.
If you win, it's up to you.
If I win,
you have to answer a question.
Ladies first.
This is how you play.
I lost.
My question is,
a life arranged by others
must be exhausting, right?
Who are you exactly?
Someone who can help you.
What do you know?
I understand your discontent.
You're capable,
but trapped in marriage.
You work
hard on your own,
yet people point fingers and say
it's all because of your parents.
You know me well.
You want to resist,
but you can't, right?
Actually, life is like snooker.
Sometimes,
mistakes
are the best offense.
You're drunk.
How about we
go somewhere else to sober up?
You know,
some people
are born to live in the fire.
Either they are burnt to ashes,
or they temper themselves into a sword.
Guess
which one I am.
Your heart is beating so fast.
Is it because of desire,
or
because you smell a familiar scent?
Shh.
Don't answer so quickly.
Tonight,
I'll let you win.
Good night,
Mr. Heir.
I hope your dreams
are cleaner than mine.